{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 37,
                "_id": "02-01",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "What includes the integrated application of resources to improve public safety through minimizing the probability or occurrence and/or the impact of unfortunate events?",
                "refPage": "47",
                "possible0": "Potential critical incident",
                "possible1": "Community risk reduction",
                "possible2": "Occupational safety standards",
                "possible3": "Emergency response capabilities",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "_id": "02-02",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "The CRR process works to improve public safety by coordinating emergency operations with _____ efforts in the community and at the fire station.",
                "refPage": "47",
                "possible0": "succession planning",
                "possible1": "diversity and inclusion",
                "possible2": "prevention and mitigation",
                "possible3": "nonemergency public interaction",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "_id": "02-03",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Proper community risk assessment considers the frequency of the:",
                "refPage": "51",
                "possible0": "risks becoming hazards.",
                "possible1": "data collection methods used.",
                "possible2": "public complaints and inquiries.",
                "possible3": "community and district surveys.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "_id": "02-04",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "When interacting with the public, it is important to:",
                "refPage": "51",
                "possible0": "refer any resident who is being difficult to the organization's PIO.",
                "possible1": "resolve issues within your authority or know who to contact for help.",
                "possible2": "prioritize complaints and issues according to the area where the resident lives.",
                "possible3": "ask anyone who is angry to leave, calm down, then return when they are less angry.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "_id": "02-05",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Some locations that present safety and health risks for a community are referred to as:",
                "refPage": "52",
                "possible0": "target hazards.",
                "possible1": "specialized hazards.",
                "possible2": "high risk/low frequency areas.",
                "possible3": "high/low occupancy dwellings.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "_id": "02-06",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Community risk assessment should include planning for different _____ based on a community's location, environment, and other factors.",
                "refPage": "53",
                "possible0": "data analysis",
                "possible1": "natural disasters",
                "possible2": "public complaints",
                "possible3": "standard operating procedures",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "_id": "02-07",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Which CRR strategy is intended to inform the public and/or advocate for fire and life safety behavioral change?",
                "refPage": "53",
                "possible0": "Education",
                "possible1": "Economics",
                "possible2": "Engineering",
                "possible3": "Enforcement",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "_id": "02-08",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Which CRR strategies do not depend primarily on human factors but rather are built into the environment?",
                "refPage": "55",
                "possible0": "Economic-based",
                "possible1": "Education-based",
                "possible2": "Engineering-based",
                "possible3": "Enforcement-based",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "_id": "02-09",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Which CRR strategy refers to codes, ordinances, and public policies that reduce risk for the community and have the force of law?",
                "refPage": "56",
                "possible0": "Education",
                "possible1": "Economics",
                "possible2": "Engineering",
                "possible3": "Enforcement",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "_id": "02-10",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "Insurance premium cost savings for the installation of safety devices would be considered _____ to encourage individuals and the community to implement positive risk reduction practices.",
                "refPage": "56",
                "possible0": "compliance",
                "possible1": "noncompliance",
                "possible2": "economic incentives",
                "possible3": "education incentives",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "_id": "02-11",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "What is the least cost-effective prevention and mitigation CRR strategy that must be available at every moment in communities?",
                "refPage": "57",
                "possible0": "Education",
                "possible1": "Engineering",
                "possible2": "Emergency response",
                "possible3": "Economic assessment",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "_id": "02-12",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "As part of a community risk assessment (CRA), fire and life safety educators are expected to have a thorough understanding of a community's _____, including population distribution, social and cultural influences, and educational levels.",
                "refPage": "58",
                "possible0": "economy",
                "possible1": "vulnerability",
                "possible2": "demographics",
                "possible3": "mitigation strategy",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "_id": "02-13",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "It is important for a fire and life safety organization to consider the impact a risk is having or potentially having over a specific population when:",
                "refPage": "59",
                "possible0": "reaching consensus.",
                "possible1": "focusing on ramifications.",
                "possible2": "assessing vulnerability to risk.",
                "possible3": "socioeconomic brackets change.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "_id": "02-14",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "What will never be completely eradicated no matter how well organized and resource-equipped a risk-mitigation strategy may be?",
                "refPage": "60",
                "possible0": "Reliable data sources",
                "possible1": "Objective evaluations",
                "possible2": "Preventable occurrences",
                "possible3": "Measurable levels of reduction",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "_id": "02-15",
                "chapterId": 2,
                "question": "What establishes a desired level of measurable reduction for a specific risk over a set amount of time?",
                "refPage": "60",
                "possible0": "Outcome reports",
                "possible1": "Level of resources",
                "possible2": "Learning objective",
                "possible3": "Problem statement and goal",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
